europeforvisitors.com 2002-06-10

# Privacy Policy

| | 

**Privacy Policy**

Europe for Visitors, Venice for Visitors, Switzerland for Visitors, and Austria for Visitors have a very simple privacy policy:

  * We don't gather any personal information from you. Even if we learn personal information about you (such as your e-mail address, if you write to us), we won't share that information with anyone else. We won't "spam" you with e-mail sales pitches, either.

**Notes:**

  * We aren't responsible for information that may be gathered by ad networks, affiliates, or advertisers when you complete surveys or fill out order forms. Nor are we responsible for any of the "cookies" that marketers and other linked sites may place in your "temporary Internet files" directory to keep track (for example) of whether we're entitled to a commission on your purchase of an auto rental or rail pass.

  * When you visit a Web site (ours or anybody else's), the Web site's server logs indicate where you came from--e.g., "aol.com," "att.net," "harvard.edu," "fritolay.com," or "hkcable.com.hk." However, the server log doesn't indicate who you are, and we have no way of knowing your identity.

| |  |    | 

** **

**Car Rentals**

Rent cars, RVs, and cell phones from a company with 47 years in Europe. Peugeot leases are also available.

Driving 17 days or longer? A short-term lease is cheaper than renting.

* * *

**Rail Travel**

Rail passes, Rail 'n Drive, and tickets for 60 European railroads.

* * *

**Hotels**

Great rates, with hotel ratings and reviews by readers. See my booking tips.

**Travel Intelligence**  
Get preferred rates at first-class and luxury hotels in Europe for stays of 3+ nights.

* * *

**Sightseeing**

**Viator**  
Book hundreds of city tours, day trips, boat cruises, etc. online.

* * *

**Air/Packages**

Buy a money-saving air/land package, or design your own.

**Expedia.co.uk**  
Air tickets and holiday packages for British travelers.

* * *

**Insurance**

**Use the automated quote form to compare 29 plans.  
  
---|---
